2321 E Wendell Ave 89101, Las Vegas, Nevada

## **Profile**

I'm a motivated 19 year old that's ready to take a career serious. I always seek to provide people with value by really understanding their needs and earning their business. Financial freedom will always be a goal of mine and I do everything it takes to continue to grow to provide for others and my family.

# Experience

SALES REPRESENTATIVE, VIVINT; USA - 2020-PRESENT

I'm responsible for traveling around the US and knock door to door with the smart home company Vivint. I run a small sales team and I'm responsible for finding and closing leads, recruiting new employees and solving problems.

CALL CENTER / CUSTOMER SERVICE, DIAMOND RESORTS, LAS VEGAS, NV - 2019-2020

At this job I was responsible for answering inbound calls and booking vacation reservations over the phone. I made sure I always put the customer first and handled their problems in a professional manner.

LANDSCAPER, JUANS LANDSCAPING, LAS VEGAS, NV - 2018-2019

When I was a landscaper I was responsible for carrying palm tree leaves and throwing them in a trailer, mowing grass and cleaning up any trash that was gathered by a leaf blower.

### Education

Rancho, Las Vegas, Nevada – High School Diploma, Class of 2019

#### Skills

Door to door sales

Communication skills

Labor intensive work

#### References

Jan Peterson, Vivint Sales Manager / +1 (651) 274-4795

Greg Jacobsen, Vivint Sales Manager / +1 (435) 671-8567